oneprojectcloser.com 2016-03-09

# Privacy Policy for One Project Closer - One Project Closer

This Privacy Policy covers [http://www.oneprojectcloser.com](http://www.oneprojectcloser.com/) and all content on this site, collectively known as **One Project Closer** and **One Project Closer, The Better Half.**

**Your Privacy is Important to Us!**

At One Project Closer, we recognize that privacy of your personal information is important. Here is information on what types of personal information we receive and collect when you use visit our sites, and how we safeguard your information. We never sell your personal information to third parties.

**1\. Log Files:** As with most other websites, we collect and use the data contained in log files. The information in the log files include your IP (internet protocal) address, your ISP (internet service provider, such as AOL or Shaw Cable), the browser you used to visit our site (such as Internet Explorer or Firefox), the time you visited our site, the search engine you used to find us (if any) and which pages you visited throughout our site. We may collect anonymous usage data beyond these specific details shown here.

**2\. Cookies and Beacons:** We do use cookies to store information, such as your personal preferences when you visit our site. This could include only showing you a popup once in your visit, or the ability to login to some of our features, such as forums.

**3\. Third Party Advertisements:** We also use third party advertisements on to support our sites. Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, your ISP , the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed. This is generally used for geotargeting purposes (showing New York real estate ads to someone in New York, for example) or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as showing cooking ads to someone who frequents cooking sites).

**4\. Registering with Our Site:** We do not disclose personal information you provide when you register for an account on our site, except that we may display any username you provide.

**5\. Further Protecting Your Privacy:** You can chose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites. This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts.

**6\. Terms and Conditions:** Your use of our web site is governed entirely by our [Terms and Conditions](http://www.oneprojectcloser.com/terms-and-conditions/). When there is a conflict between this privacy policy and our terms and conditions, our terms and conditions supercede this policy. You may wish to review our terms and conditions before you use any information or services provided by our site.

Thanks for visiting One Project Closer. Please feel free to e-mail [editors@oneprojectcloser.com](mailto:editors@oneprojectcloser.com) if you’ve any questions or concerns.
